Thank you for watching!
Hallo! Ste. is about to start!
This time we have Akari Uemura of Juice-Juice with us on Halo! Ste this time with Akari Uemura of Juice-Juice,
BEYOOOOONDS, Mamoru Ameno, and Momohime Kiyama of Kawami.
We will be presenting with these two.
Please stay with us until the end.
Now, both Juice-Juice and BEYOOOOONDS are in the middle of their spring tour!
are in the middle of their spring tours!
So, we are Juice- Juice Spencer Anniversary Concert Tour
We are doing Juice-Juice, though,
Juice-Juice has 10 members now.
The two new members are getting used to each other, and I think this tour has broadened the scope of Juice-Juice.
How about BEYOOOOONDS?
BEYOOOOONDS is doing the Neovio leg of the BEYOOOOONDS concert tour,
This time, too, we are going to give a performance that will be full throttle Beyoncé style,
I hope that the 12 of us will be able to convey the goodness of our music to as many people as possible, and we are all working together to do so.
As for the tour, Juice-Juice will perform in Hokkaido this weekend,
BEYOOOOONDS is scheduled to perform in Kanagawa,
I hope we can enjoy them to the fullest.
And on May 29th, Juice-Juice will be performing at the Nippon Budokan,
And BEYOOOOONDS, too.
BEYOOOOONDS will be performing at the Nippon Budokan for the second time on May 15.
Please look forward to it as well.
Please look forward to it.
Please take a look at this video first.
Go ahead!
It's hard to see you in these times
a screen short of a string game
Poof, it's done!
the beginning of a relationship is crucial
Makeup that changes in a whirl
The ever-changing self-study
I'm tired of all the preparation
High talk gourmet tire canning
More than just enjoying the time
I'll miss you more than I'll ever miss you
I miss you more than anything in the universe
G.O.A.T. Give my love
I want to have a hot love
Hold my heart tight
I'm in love, I'm in love, I'm in love, I'm in love
I'm in love, I'm in love, I'm in love at the same time
G.O.A.T. Give my love
Give me a crush
When you're in love, you've got to get close
I'm so excited, I'm so nervous, I'm so excited, I'm so nervous
Give me a shot, give me a shot, give me a shot
At least once in your life, you feel like you're meant to be.
When you feel it, you can't give in.
I wonder if my feelings are hotter than a meteor
Even if we hurt each other
I have a feeling we'll understand each other better.
I have a feeling that we can understand each other better
G.O.A.T. Give my love
I want to have a hot love
Hold my heart tight
With a kiss that makes me soar
I'm in love, I'm in love at the same time
G.O.A.T. Give my love
Give me a crush
When you're in love, you've got to get close
I'm so excited, I'm so nervous, I'm so excited, I'm so nervous
Give me a shot, give me a shot, give me a shot
At least once in your life, you feel like you're meant to be.
When you feel it, it's non-negotiable.
I love you. I love you with all my heart.
I love you, my love.
I love you, my hero.
LaLaLaLa... G418 LaLaLa... G418 LaLaLa...
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for all your hard work.
With Akari Uemura of Juice-Juice,
BEYOOOOONDS, Mamoru Ameno, and Momohime Kiyama of Kawami. Stay!
From here, we would like to talk a little bit about each other.
I will ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer in a quick tempo.
Momohime Kiyama graduated from high school last month. How do you frankly feel now that you have graduated?
Sad.
What is your dream that you don't think will come true?
To have a Zong.
Seek! The first part of the line in question at the beginning of "Fate's Traveler".
With what consciousness are you performing?
Zon not to keep.
What hair color would you like to try?
Milk tea.
This year marks the 25th anniversary of the Hello! Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year.
Which song would Momohime Kiyama like to beat?
Morning Musume。 Project's "Shabondama".
Thank you very much for your time.
Thank you very much.
It's terrible that I graduated from high school, but I was very frank about it.
I'm really sad and I've spent my time feeling like I'm still in high school.
I have that image too.
I sometimes think that the JK brand is really precious.
And which song would you like to beat, Momohime Kiyama?
Soap bubbles.
Soap bubbles have a really cool sound behind them,
And it has stylish parts. I would like to play along with it.
So I wanted to play along with them.
I am looking forward to seeing it someday.
Questions for Mr. Uemura will be asked after the VTR.
Hello! STE.
I am Riko Yamagishi of Tsubaki Factory.
I am Yumeno Kishimoto.
We will graduate from Tsubaki Factory and Hello! Project after this year's fall tour.
It has been more than 10 years since I joined Hello!
Project trainees. Last year, during Tsubaki Factory's performance at Nippon Budokan,
Project trainees for more than 10 years, but last year when Tsubaki Factory performed at Nippon Budokan, I felt that everyone loved me so much,
I felt that I had done my best as an idol,
That's why I made the decision to graduate.
I would like to study stage performance in the future.
Until graduation, I would like to create more and more fun memories with my fans,
I would like to make more fun memories with my fans until I graduate, so please give me your best regards.
I, Kishimoto, had a dream to sing by myself someday,
But when I took a break and saw their live performances, I felt that Tsubaki Factory is a strong group,
I was able to decide to graduate from Tsubaki Factory.
After graduation, I will continue to express myself through music,
I would like to express myself more than ever through music, and also do various activities such as fashion and fitness.
I will continue to do my best to leave a meaningful legacy to the group for the rest of my time until graduation.
We will do our best until graduation, so please continue to support us.
BEYOOOOONDS New Single Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler Now on Tour
I have the night sky now that I can't pollute it
BEYOOOOONDS New Single
I can't even draw a dream in the night sky
Now on sale
Suteki na HUMAN LIFE
I can't lose ahead of you
Regretful and Emotionless
Angerme New Album Big Love
Now on sale
Halo! Sta.
Next, I would like to ask a question to Ms. Uemura.
Are you ready?
I'm fine.
Uemura-san, you are a photography enthusiast, what is the subject you want to take pictures of?
I got a film camera, so I want to take pictures of the members.
What is the first thing that comes to mind when you look back over the past 10 years?
The 10th anniversary event.
What do you want to improve yourself for the next 10 years?
Makeup.
What is your favorite way to apply makeup?
I'm addicted to makeup using colored eye shadow and mascara.
What song from Hello! Project's history best fits your current state of mind?
Rain
Rain is on my mind.
I heard it was raining outside at the time of recording.
It wasn't raining when I was coming here, so I didn't bring an umbrella.
So I'm going home today feeling like I want to get wet even though the rain is cold.
I thought to myself, "It's now!
It's now.
I was also curious about your favorite makeup method.
How many colors of makeup do you use?How many colors of makeup do you sometimes use?
I use a pink colored mascara for Akane Haga of Morning Musume。 23's Akemi Haga gave me a pink colored mascara.
She gave me a stylish colored mascara.
I haven't often bought mascara for myself, so I thought I'd like to try different kinds of makeup with it.
I wanted to try out different kinds of makeup with it, so I've been using it.
I learned a lot about the fashionable Ms. Uemura.
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much! Stay tuned for more after this!
Tea Horse
This is Nanami Kubota from Tea Horse.
I will continue to do my best with love as before.
What are you cooking today?
Today it's pasta with bacon and mushrooms in tomato sauce!
I'm tearing up!
From the bottom to the top
It's going to be delicious!
Oh, no, no, no. It's this way.
Sorry.
This tomato has skin and seeds in it, so just pop it in.
A little bit of handle.
In this state, it's not a sauce.
We're going to have to strain it.
Do you want me to mash them?
Yeah, mash it.
Just the skin and the seeds.
It's hard.
Here, like this.
Ahhh...
Rebeti.
No, no, no, no, no.
There's not much of a level.
Just, like, squeeze it here.
Put this on while you're at it.
Okay, one more time.
Here.
It's on here.
Oh, that one, too?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What a waste of time.
The ones that came through.
Yes, sir.
Here we go.
Only the skin and sauce are left.
Shall I cut it?
Like this... one quarter.
Like this
Like this.
Even I can do it.
This is easy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm relieved to hear it. These cute little mushrooms. Mushrooms. Mushrooms.
I like bacon. I'm going to keep going. That's about right.
It's starting to look like this. It smells so good. One more.
It's sweet, isn't it? I like the smell, too.
Beautiful. Candy color. I always say that about the other one, it's candy color.
Here's a tomato.
Garlic first.
This one's like candy.
This tobetto is good. It's delicious.
It still takes time. Pasta is hard.
It takes a long time to make the tomato sauce, so we make a lot of it and keep it in stock.
Maybe you're doing it, Mom.
Make double or triple the amount.
The tomato sauce is simmering down, so we'll taste it once.
I think it's probably very sweet.
Oh, it's sweet.
I don't think it's salty enough.
I think it's not salty enough.
About two pinches.
Yes, you're right.
A little less salt.
Just right.
A little bit of olive oil.
Mix it with this.
Yes, just mix it.
It looks like a lot of oil.
But it blends really well.
Tomato sauce.
The color is totally different from the first color, isn't it?
Is it heavy? No, it's a little heavy, but it's not.
No, it's not. I didn't do it on purpose.
This one might be really heavy.
Iron is heavy.
It's really heavy.
Can you do it? Yes!
If we open it like this! There's a lot of people on it!
It's so heavy!
It's good to do it like this. Doing it by myself.
It looks good.
What if I try to hold it with my left hand?
Impossible!
I'm surprised now.
Motosauce is done!
Finished!
OK.
Wow!
That's about a little more than a tablespoon.
Well, about 1 tablespoon.
I think it's a bit much.
The mushrooms soak up all the oil.
Oh, wow.
They're cute. I want to get a nice brown color.
You don't want to touch them too much. They're bouncing all over the place.
Hold it like this. Slowly. Are they browned?
Yes, it's browning.
Pine.
It's all set.
The lemon, it's especially moist.
It's easy to get bouncy.
If I make this all by myself...
I'm going to get burned.
What kind of a mess...
Burn? It's a pain in the ass.
I used to make frozen bread.
It's so hard to cook.
If I'm alone, it gets burnt.
I get lazy.
I just...
I'd just press the button and leave it alone.
I leave it alone.
Oh, that's right.
I'm good at cooking eggs.
Omelets?
Or steamed eggs.
That's great.
I can cook an omelet.
The kind you roll up?
Yes, I can.
That's amazing.
I used to make my own lunch in high school.
I used to make it myself freshman year.
That's great.
I make sabayaki every day.
You don't mind if I say the bottom is starting to stick together a little?
Don't worry about it.
But if you cook it over high heat.
But if you cook it on high heat, it gets burnt and has a bitter taste.
But in this state, it's a mass of flavor.
We shouldn't be too careless.
Yes, yes, yes.
The right amount of heat.
You can see the color coming out of the bacon.
The oil from the bacon is also good for the marshmallows.
It's a good match?
Yes, it works well.
I used to do this a lot, and the bottom would get all scorched up.
You want to take the top off and wash the bottom pan, don't you?
The skinny part is the best part.
If you put this tomato sauce in here, you can take it out.
I baked it normally, so I think it's fine like that.I baked it like normal, so I guess that's how it's supposed to be.
I think I got some of the skinny.
I think I got some of it off.
You got it, didn't you?
It's the flavor of the tomato sauce.
It's a little thick right now.
But I'm going to put some of the cooking water in here, so it'll be just right.
It'll be just right.
It's just perfect.
It's good.
It's glowing.
That's important.
It's the oil that reflects the light.
The oil is delicious.
Oh, wow!
Wow!
Ha-ha-ha!
Whoo-hoo!
Wow!
I was really looking forward to seeing the finished product.
Cooking is exciting and you don't get to see the members cooking unless it's a project like this,
It motivates me to try cooking different kinds of dishes.
Do you cook anything?
I do a lot of cooking, but it's not so much that I make anything special,
I like to keep a variety of recipes and cook a week's worth of dishes, such as this one today and this one today.
Wow. That's amazing. I had never thought of a plan.
I'm still not very good at cooking, so I'm not very good at it.
I'm trying to get better at miso soup.
I can make miso soup well.
Oh! What do you like to put in it? Ingredients.
It may be a little surprising or unusual, but I like to put lettuce in it.
Lettuce? Lettuce in miso soup, which doesn't work very well.
Lettuce is quite tasty,
Does it retain its crunchiness?
But both crispy and crunchy are good, aren't they? With lettuce.
So, I think I can eat it as long as it's warmed up, no matter when it's cooked.
Oh, that's good.
Both are delicious.
I'd like to try it.
Please try it.
I think.
Hallo! Ste!
Next is the presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart.
So, I think Hello! Project really has a lot of great songs,
Project has many great songs, but the one that really struck a chord with me recently is the one that I thought was so true once again,
Project has a lot of great songs, but the one that really struck a chord with me recently was one of our own Juice-Juice songs,
I want to do this and that,
I want to do this and that, but there is not enough time,
I have been thinking lately that 24 hours is really short,
I have not really thought about it much until now.
I haven't lived a life where I was pressed for time so much,
But recently, I have been thinking, "What? I have to go to bed at this late hour,
I'm having a hard time,
It's a lot of work, and I feel like I don't have enough time to do everything I want to do.
Today is the day I think about,
It's from BEYOOOOONDS's new single,
There is a lyric, "In a night sky where you can't even draw a dream,
It's my part, but there is a lyric that says, "So many stars love you,
I thought it was a really good lyric,
I think it's a really good lyric, and I put my heart and soul into singing it, hoping that the listeners will feel the same way.
It's romantic.
It's romantic, isn't it? I like it very much.
Please watch the VTR. Please watch the VTR.
Presentation of lyrics that touched my heart
In this corner, we will present the lyrics of the songs of Hello!
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics. Project's songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Utaina Satoyoshi, would like to make a presentation.
Here we go. Here it is.
You should play with your face as it is! I won't make it easy for you!
These are the lyrics of the song "Mirror Mirror" by Angerme.
I think there are many lyrics in the world that have messages such as "be yourself as you are" or "be yourself,
But when I wonder what constitutes being yourself as you are, what is it that makes you who you are?
But when I wondered what I mean by "just as I am", I thought that forcing myself to show my true self, the self I don't want to show, is not "just as I am,
I want to show the self that I want to show, the self that I want to be. I want to show them the me I want to show them, the me I want to be,
I want to show myself as I want to show myself, as I want to be.
I don't want to force myself to compete without any makeup,
I want to show that I have these weapons and that I have armed myself in this way,
I thought it would be better to survive by using everything I have and the knowledge I have acquired.
Seeing this, I thought that it would be better to use everything I have and the knowledge I have acquired to survive.
Yes, yes, yes.
I think the lyrics will give people who are torn by their identities the confidence to use their skills and favorite things and go on strong.
The song itself is a lyric about the real me, or a lyric that says, "Look at the real me,
It is interesting that this lyric comes in the first A melody of the song.
I thought it was interesting that the lyric "I won't show you who I really am," and then the lyric "Look at me, the real me.
The song ends with Mr. Kamen Kyokuryo saying, "You're the one who sees through me," after he has been telling me to see through someone all along,
I was wondering if you were me when I first heard the song,
I thought he was talking to his reflection in the mirror, and then the lyrics here were interpreted in a very different way,
I thought it was an interesting lyric,
That's why I like this song.
I read too much into it.
We don't often sing songs about strong women like this in Beyond.
I hope that someday, as we grow up, we will be suited to this kind of song,
I am pleased to introduce these lyrics to you.
So, please look forward to the next installment!
Hallo! STE!
Akari Uemura of Juice-Juice and Momohime Kiyama of BEYOOOOONDS's Amemori Kawami present "Halo! STE!
As I mentioned at the beginning of this article, the Beyoncé will be performing at the Nippon Budokan for the second time on May 15.
Beyons Concert Tour NeoBio at Budokan will be held on May 15. Yes, and Juice-Juice will be performing at the Nippon Budokan on May 29.
What kind of place is the Nippon Budokan?
This is my second time to perform at the Nippon Budokan, but last year was my first time. I was really surprised at the size of the building, and even when I saw it, I felt it was huge.
Nervous? Always.
Yes, I do.
I get nervous. You seem to have an image of being imposing.
Really? I'm really nervous, and I'm good at making a face that isn't nervous.
You are so good at it! Then I think you are very good at it.
Well, for me, the Nippon Budokan is not just the size of the hall, but also the feeling of looking up and seeing everyone looking at you, and the sense of applause falling on you, which I think is an atmosphere unique to the Nippon Budokan.
The first time you performed at the Budokan was also memorable, but how do you feel about the second time?
I learned a lot more from the first time than the second time, so I can use what I learned the first time to improve my performance, such as how to use my body, or how to use my muscles in a way that makes them more fearful,
You understood it the first time? You have a lot of leeway.
I noticed that the back of my neck was really tight.
I noticed the tightness.
Is that so? That's tough. I feel like I sing better when I stretch the back of my neck,
That's great.
It's coming out this way, but I'm surprised it's not hitting me,
That feeling is amazing.
Really? So I'm anxious to do well, but I hope I can do my best.
Project's Budokan, even though I've been waiting for it to start with high expectations,
Project, I think that the performance of each group exceeds the expectations,
I think we, Juice-Juice, will do our best as well.
BEYOOOOONDS will be performing with the Pacific Philharmonia Pops Tokyo on May 2,
We will also hold a biophonic concert.
We hope you will enjoy our relaxed atmosphere.
Please look forward to this event as well.
Love is the big bang The beginning of a story
The best part is that even though the time has passed
Don't look at me like I'm still unknown
When you are rich, you can even go to outer space
Now is still infinite
Now is just a blink of an eye, so...
So bring it all together
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I want to bring it all together and start with what I want to say
I love you on a cosmic scale I love you on a cosmic scale I love you on a cosmic scale I love you on a cosmic scale
I was born on this planet You Say Yes
To make love come true
Rapid Topic 1 The Beginning of a Story The Beginning
You can't measure it by the number of root buttons
Both are one and the same, and both are possible
Even though our backs are against each other
In an era of fragmentation
Let's just focus on what's going on in each other's lives
We're all special.
We're the best.
We can do what we want to do, as much as we want to do it
I want to do what I want to do. I want to do what I want to do.
On a cosmic scale.
I love it! I love it! I love it!
I say yes!
I say YES!
I'm sure it's just rightIt must be just right.
Just because we live in a time like this
We're not giving up
On a cosmic scale
I love you
Since the day you raised your voice
You say yes!
When the time came, we were connected
Rabbit Big Bang
from our friends to our friends
I thought on a cosmic scale
It's amazing to be here
Probability. The universe at large.
I mean, there's only three of us.
But we're all bound together by our hearts.
That's the knoll.
Until the middle of my dreams.
I love you.
Declaration.
All my life
The Journey Begins
I say YES!
I want to write it all down
I want to start with the feelings I want to convey
To the middle of the dream
I love you, I love you, I love you
I was born on this planet
We say YES! Love is the big one!
Love is the big one!
[Applause]
Let's do our best tomorrow!
With Akari Uemura of Juice-Juice,
BEYOOOOONDS, and Meimihime Kiyama of Morikami Ameno. Stay!
It's time for us to say goodbye.
Here's an announcement!
BEYOOOOONDS's new single, Seek Me, Fate's Traveler
In the night sky where even dreams cannot be drawn... was released last week!
Yes, it's here...
I just realized something again...
Everyone in BEYOOOOONDS sings so well!
They are so good!
I've had a lot of inspiration within my own group.
I felt it in this 4th single as well.
I hope you will enjoy their singing voices!
And BEYOOOOONDS 2nd concert tour
The Blu-ray of "BEYOOOOONDS's 2nd Concert Tour in Autumn" is now on sale!
This is the Blu-ray of last fall's tour.
Not only the performance of course, but also the hair and makeup of BEYOOOOONDS.
I hope you will pay attention to BEYOOOOONDS's hair and makeup.
I'd like you to take a look at it.
Project 2023 Spring City Circuit is underway!
Juice-Juice will perform in Hokkaido on April 23rd, and BEYOOOOONDS will perform on April 22nd.
BEYOOOOONDS will perform in Kanagawa on April 22!
Yes, BEYOOOOONDS will perform at Nippon Budokan on May 15!
And Juice-Juice is also scheduled to perform at the Nippon Budokan on May 29!
So, I am looking forward to this day and will do my best in preparation and rehearsal.
Yes, we will do our best!
And on May 2, we will be holding a biophonic concert at the Tokyo Metropolitan Art Space.
Please look forward to it as well!
Hello! Project members will appear on this channel more and more!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
We are still in the midst of an exciting time, but let's get through it together!
With us are Akari Uemura of Juice-Juice and Momohime Kiyama of BEYOOOOONDS Ame no Mori Kawao!
Goodbye.